I always hope that you remember
We'll never really learn the meaning of it all
What we have is strong and tender
So hold on
In the middle of the madness
When the time is running out and you're left alone
All I want is you to know that
It's strong still
Can't pull us apart
Nothing can come, nothing can come
Nothing can come between us
Baby, nothing can come, nothing can come
I always hope that you remember
What we have is strong and tender
In the middle of the madness, hold on
So it truly is a good thing
And I always wanted you to know
There is always this, and this is everlasting
Hold on
It's about faith
It's about trust
Nothing can come, nothing can come
Nothing can come between us
Baby, nothing can come, nothing can come
Can come (Nothing can come)
Nothing can come
Can tear (Nothing can come between us)
Can pull (Nothing can come)
Nothing can come
Us apart (Nothing can come between us)
Can come (Nothing can come)
Nothing can come
Can tear (Nothing can come between us)
Can pull (Nothing can come)
Nothing can come
Us apart (Nothing can come between us)